In this way we are
getting information from Reuters. Now I want to query
why they had taken out an eye on the day of lifting and had kept a target of 12 on it,
they have reduced it from 1280 to 900 rupees
per share. Today you will see their team, the
rate was 15-1600 when the
report of goat rains came and the
stop has reached almost 12 class but today
they have once again
maintained the sell rating of the stock and cut the target by
about 25% and have set a new target at 9. If
this first report is
correct then the price, the sales
multiple of Paytm is more than 12 times, it is
inflationary in terms of valuation.
Apart from this, if you look at the company's gas and the
company's profit on the project, then it will take
many years, this is a
compulsion to believe and I keep my
negative, here the
target has been reduced once again to use
that we are behind and on the spot of hotels
or you seem to be quite active on that
and are based on
Gemini Gemini has been torn ever since its listing in the Supreme Court. In
terms of valuation, many people are worried about it,
which seems expensive or cheap. As far as the
Best Scenario Printer is concerned,
here UBS's lowest target is
around ₹3000 and as far as the job is
concerned, from here also they feel that there is a
20% upside in the stock and
with a target of around ₹5450, they have
advised buying. Morning salary is also for the
staff police, the target is around ₹4338.
If we talk about doctor performance, then
perhaps the profit blue has been admitted
because the pressure is being created on this bundle,
but going forward, because
you can see the inflation rate increasing, it will
not benefit the company at all,
you will see revenue growth coming from inflation.
Apart from this, UBS
believes that the future of this company will be
worth watching because the
problems, especially the problems that were created today by
other products from Amazon, there is
competition in front of such commerce, that is one  It will be
something worth watching and
we have updated the question here with the help of
any holding. They feel
that the margins of this product are
under some pressure due to this, but going forward
you will probably see some improvement in the margins
and inflation will show the company's top line
increasing. So what has been
said in this, but
as far as the license number is concerned, there is
some discomfort from the brokerages regarding safe valuation,
but in the case of the group, there are many people who
feel that yes, there is a lot of
scope. JP Morgan's target is yes
and Rs 1580. If you look at the fundamentals, the
companies are quite strong, the demand for insurance has
also increased significantly, but
JP Morgan believes that its low
valuations are quite expensive and you may
get group opportunities, but in
terms of valuation, there is some upside limited in the stock.
We think
you will see the sector outlook improving in the
year 2009.
If you look at it further, the return on equity of the company can be up
to 20% and JP
Morgan believes  So let's go ahead and
review this target and our rating, the
volume is a little different from the first Saturday, the stock is a little
different, this strategy is fixed Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal